- [EMT] Make way! Clear a path!
- [nurse] Coming through! Excuse me.
- [EMT] Coming through!
- [nurse] Make way! Excuse me.
[muffled] Make way! Move aside!
Clear a path! Please make way!
[nurse] We have an emergency!
She's heavily pregnant!
She was in an accident.
[tense music playing]
- [nurse 1] BP 80/50. Pulse 130.
- [nurse 2] Have you drawn the labs?
[nurse 1] They've been sent.
[nurse 2] IV is running.
Sat's dropping to 88.
The doctor is here.
[doctor] How does the fetal heart sound?
[nurse 2] It sounds faint.
[nurse 3] Sat's down to 75.
[doctor] Get the FAST.
[nurse 2] Go get the FAST!
[weakly] Please, save my baby.
[nurse 3] Her consciousness is dropping.
[doctor] FAST is positive.
Notify the OR. Don't wait.
[music concludes]
[Yupin speaking indistinctly]
The other car was going very fast.
[sniffles]
The police said the driver was drunk.
When I got to the hospital… [sniffles]
…I was rushed in
for an emergency C-section.
[sobs softly]
I didn't even get to see my baby's face.
[whimpers]
And my baby…
Witness, when did you find out
that your baby's body was missing?
[sniffles]
[exhales]
On the day of the cremation,
I asked to have the coffin opened.
But…
the undertaker wouldn't let me see.
So I had to threaten to call the police.
That's when he finally admitted to me…
[sniffles]
…that he took my baby's body
and sold it to that man, Boonlue.
[sinister music playing]
This image is from Exhibit VJ-7.
It shows the defendant's monastery
during the police raid.
Witness, have you ever been there?
Please tell the court about it.
[Yupin] Yes.
I went there looking for my baby.
With the police.
[lawyer] From Exhibits VJ-8
through VJ-12…
Witness, do you know
what is in these photos?
[sniffles]
[breathes shakily]
That's my baby.
- [music intensifies]
- [Yupin] He turned him into a luk krok.
My baby…
He was inside me for nine months.
[sobs]
But in the end…
You!
You turned my son into a talisman
and sold him!
How could you do that, you bastard?!
Witness, compose yourself.
[Yupin] That was my son!
I lost both my son and my husband!
Are you even human, you animal?!
Damn you to hell!
Yupin.
Calm down. Calm down, Yupin.
Calm down.
- [music fades]
- [breathes shakily]
[sniffles]
No further questions.
The defense may cross-examine.
Does the defense have no questions?
No questions, Your Honor.
- [judge] Are you sure?
- [Jittri] Yes, Your Honor.
[unsettling music playing]
[judge] Call the next witness.
Witness, what is your connection
to this case?
I'm the doctor who delivered the baby
by C-section after the accident.
[lawyer] And what was
the fetus's condition at that time?
Critical. The mother's uterus
had ruptured.
The mother was losing a lot of blood.
If we didn't operate immediately,
there was a high probability
that we would lose them both.
But as we all know,
in the end, we were only able
to save the mother.
And what happened to the baby after that?
[doctor] We informed the mother
that the body was still at the hospital
before it was sent
to the temple where the incident occurred.
[lawyer] No further questions.
[music fades]
[judge] Will the defense
be questioning this witness?
I will be questioning this witness myself,
Your Honor.
[high heels clacking]
[tense music playing]
After you delivered the baby,
did it make a sound?
No.
And the baby's body,
when you delivered it,
do you recall what color it was?
[high-pitched ringing]
- [footsteps approaching]
- [EKG monitor beeping]
[lights slam off]
What color was it?
Green or purple?
[doctor] It was discolored.
[Jittri] After you delivered the baby,
did it move at all?
[pediatrician] No heart rate.
Prepare for PPV.
I don't know the specifics.
I'm an obstetrician.
Once the delivery was complete,
it became
the pediatrician's responsibility.
[pediatrician] No improvement.
Prep 0.01 milligrams of adrenaline.
[Jittri] After the baby was delivered,
no matter what life-saving measures
were attempted,
a pulse was never detected.
Is that correct?
[machine beeping]
[pediatrician] Still no heart rate.
Stop resuscitation.
Please answer yes or no.
Yes.
[Jittri] Medically speaking,
an infant in this condition
is considered a stillbirth.
Yes or no?
[music rises]
[lawyer] Objection.
Counsel's question is irrelevant.
It has no bearing on the case.
The charges filed are not related
to the time of the infant's death.
I assure you,
my question is not irrelevant.
Because my point is…
How can you say the child died,
when the child was never alive?
[crowd murmuring]
[judge] Order, please.
Counselor.
Please adhere to the relevant issues.
Yes, Your Honor.
This is Ms. Yupin's medical record.
It states here that the infant
had no vital signs after birth.
So from the moment of birth,
the infant was already deceased.
Is that correct?
[judge] Witness.
Don't look at anyone else.
Just answer the question truthfully.
That's correct.
[Jittri] Please record that, Your Honor.
[judge] Infant had
no vital signs after birth,
meaning the infant was deceased.
[Jittri] These are images
of a stillborn infant
who died before attaining
legal personhood.
Legal personhood begins when a child
is born and survives delivery.
In Ms. Yupin's case, after the delivery,
the doctor detected no pulse.
There were no signs of life
while it was still in the womb.
That means the infant that was delivered
cannot be legally defined as a corpse,
but rather, as remains,
which is no different from
a scrap of flesh.
- [music darkens]
- [crowd gasping]
[crowd murmuring]
[lawyer] Are you calling a child
who was weeks away from being born
a scrap of flesh?
We're talking about a human being.
Any birth certificate?
If you claim these remains are a person.
- [music falls]
- I'm aware my words may sound harsh.
But believe me when I say I do sympathize.
I see my own assistant,
cherishing the child in her womb
every day.
Do you really think I don't understand
what it feels like to become a mother?
How profound that feeling is?
Objection. The defense is twisting
the law to suit her.
Her interpretation is inadmissible.
Whether this is a matter of legal debate
is for the court to decide.
Counselor, you may proceed.
Then I have one final question.
The prosecution has filed charges
under Section 199
and Section 366, subsection 3,
for desecration of a corpse.
If it's proven these are merely remains,
would that constitute a false indictment
and require this case to be dismissed?
[music rises]
[music crescendoes]
[music fades]
[Boonlue] Impressive.
Excellent work.
Okay, that's all for now.
Mr. Suwat sends his thanks.
He'd like you to join him for wine
at his home in Prachinburi.
There are plenty of other cases
he'd like your help with.
Of course.
So, when are you due?
Please let him know
that I will contact his secretary myself.
Alright. Be sure to get in touch.
I will.
I quit.
I thought working for you
would make me a better person.
But the longer I'm here,
the more I hate myself.
You're disgusting. Don't you see that?
I'm simply doing what the law allows.
If what I do is evil, then everyone
in this building is evil too. Right?
[scoffs]
[Jittri] You want to argue?
[tense music playing]
Society is screwed up
because of people like you.
Getting pregnant has made you
so sensitive.
Whatever.
But next time I have a case
involving a mother and child, I'll call.
Maybe if you're pregnant again,
we can work together.
[Jittri] Pick it up yourself.
- [music darkens]
- [detector beeping]
[reporter 1] She's here!
Ms. Jittri, a quick comment?
[reporter 2] Is it true
a politician is involved
in this infant corpse trafficking ring?
[reporter 3] There's talk on social media
about putting a bounty on you.
Does that concern you?
[reporter 4]
All these questions and no comments?
Is someone powerful
pulling the strings on this case?
Jittri! You said my baby
was just remains, not a person?
- You bitch!
- [bystander screams]
[Yupin] How could you do that?
Huh?! How could you?
- You animal! Are you happy now?
- [reporters clamoring]
[Yupin] Did you buy your law degree?
Do you have any humanity in you?
Huh? That was my child, you animal!
Are you even human?
I carried my baby for nine months!
I was about to give birth!
What is your heart made of?
My baby was right here in my womb!
Get all of this! Keep rolling!
What the hell?
- [Yupin sobbing]
- [dark intriguing music playing]
[dark intriguing music continues]
THE EVIL LAWYER
[music fades]
[brooding music playing]
[detector beeps]
[indistinct chatter]
[clerk 1] She got it all over herself.
[clerk 2] That woman
looked so angry, though.
[phone ringing]
[clerk 1] Oh my god.
- How could she not be?
- [clerk 2] Will it come off?
[clerk 1] Well, look who it is.
The celebrity.
[Mek] What are you talking about?
[clerk 1 chuckles]
- [music fades]
- This is why you're famous. Look.
You really shone on the live stream.
Can I have your autograph? [chuckles]
Man, I feel bad for her.
[clerk 2] If it were me,
she'd get more than just pig's blood.
I would've thrown in some guts too.
I don't know
how she can even sleep at night.
[Tong] Don't joke about that.
She's got a heavy caseload,
and they're all major cases.
[clerk 1] You want to be like her, huh?
Tong, look at the cases she takes on.
This time it's a shaman.
What was it last time?
[Tong] Last time was the colonel
who opened a pub for money laundering.
[clerk 2] No, you're wrong.
Before that was the tycoon who shot
his son-in-law at the wedding.
And it was that lawyer, Jittri,
who got the tycoon acquitted.
The evidence was airtight,
but she still got the defendant acquitted.
She didn't do it by the book.
True. People like that are scary.
And look, you just walked past her.
I can just wash it when I get home.
Oh, Mek, I forgot to tell you.
You only have one case left today.
The recycling plant fire case.
The plant owner is the defendant.
He's already confessed
during the investigation.
So I just have to stand there
while the defendant confesses?
Whoa, don't work yourself too hard.
The arraignment is this afternoon.
Have some water. Your mouth must be dry.
[Mek] What's this about?
How long are you going to be stuck
doing these public cases, Mek?
Anyway, what about
the Lawyers' Rights Center?
Haven't they asked you to come back?
I heard they're short-staffed.
I'm staying here.
We're short-staffed here too.
Oh, wow.
If you're heartbroken,
you can always stay here with us, son.
I'm getting back to work.
If you're looking for…
like, a girlfriend, right?
Like a new girlfriend or something.
You can ask me for help with that.
- I can find you one.
- What?
Another failed sales pitch.
- You were selling something?
- [clerk 2] Yep.
- Here, take this back.
- I can give you a discount. Mine is a…
It's a pre-order for now.
[clerk 1 mutters]
[Mek] Excuse me, are you Aon?
My name is Mek.
I'm your father's lawyer.
I've read the preliminary file, but…
Just like my dad told the police.
Whatever he said, that's what it is.
About your father's confession,
there's a part at the end that I found…
That's right. Just go with that.
Sir, I compared your father's case
to others with similar circumstances.
My dad is ready to take responsibility.
He's willing to go to prison.
So can we just get this over with?
What I'm trying to say is,
the maximum sentence is seven years.
And the file says, at your father's age
and his current health,
prison will be hard on him.
Listen, kid.
I have a job to get to too.
I don't have to be in court
every day like you.
What's your problem?
Don't you want this to end quickly, huh?
Trying to get more court fees?
My dad already confessed.
Just go in there and look the part.
So we can get it done.
[intriguing music playing]
[Aon] Did you transfer it yet?
Case number O.12/2568.
Mr. Panitarn Boonprayook,
the Managing Director
of Rungruang E-waste Recycling Factory.
The prosecutor has filed charges
of criminal negligence causing a fire.
Resulting in the death of another person.
And loss of property.
The penalty is up to seven years in prison
and a fine of up to 140,000 baht.
In addition, the victims have gathered
to file for damages
for an additional ten million baht.
The plaintiff's attorney
is present for the civil case,
which is related to the criminal case.
- [music fades]
- Yes, Your Honor.
This case involves
a large number of victims.
And I have been appointed
to represent them in this lawsuit.
Does the defendant plead guilty
or not guilty?
Guilty.
If I may, Your Honor.
Uh, may I have a moment
to speak with my client?
You may.
Sir, did the other lawyer say
anything to you?
If you didn't do it, you have to say so.
I can help you.
[Techin] The defendant confessed
during the initial investigation.
That shows he feels remorse.
And he truly wants to take responsibility.
I don't know what tricks
you're trying, counselor.
But even if you get him off,
he'll live with the guilt for life,
which might be even worse than prison.
[judge] So, does the defendant
stand by his statement?
Sir…
Yes, Your Honor.
I plead guilty to all charges.
Why the hell are you so invested in this?
It's a public defender case.
Just get it over with.
So you can move on to other cases.
And you? Don't you feel a damn thing?
You just sent that man to prison.
Whoa, hold on. You've got it all wrong.
What am I supposed to feel?
The man confessed. You also heard him.
Look at him. Does he look like
a factory owner to you?
Wow, Mek. You've really changed.
Judging people
by their appearance now? [chuckles]
Shouldn't a human rights lawyer
be more PC?
Ever heard of "Gold wrapped in rags"?
Come on, man. What are you so mad about?
The villagers got their compensation,
and you get paid.
Isn't that a good thing?
Look at you, you're wasting away.
Oh, you poor thing.
You really think this is over?
You just wait.
[foreboding music playing]
Where should I wait for you, Mek?
Right here? Or inside the courtroom?
It's hot out here.
For an update on the story,
regarding the fire
at the e-waste recycling plant,
- Rungruang E-Waste Recycling.
- [intriguing music playing]
[reporter] The incident caused
extensive damage to the residents
of the Lat Krabang community.
Legal proceedings are now underway
against the factory's owner
on charges of arson.
- [music fades]
- [metal clanging]
[overlapping chatter]
[man] Please form a line. Right this way.
- [reporter] One more photo, please.
- Of course.
- [camera shutters clicking]
- [soft tense music playing]
RUAM THAI PARTY
DONATES 1,000,000 BAHT
[reporter] Okay, we're all set.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Don't go yet, sweetie.
Come take a photo with the director.
I'd rather check on the villagers, Mom.
In case they have more complaints.
- Alright. I'll call you later.
- Excuse me.
[speaks indistinctly]
Oh, okay. Please, come forward.
- [music fades]
- [birds chirping]
[Ang] From the Ruam Thai Party,
this is our help center's number.
- You can call anytime.
- Thank you.
From Dr. Atchara of the Ruam Thai Party.
It's our party's help center.
You can call the number on the card.
This is the number for our help center.
If you need anything else,
please contact the party.
- [woman 1] Get over here!
- [woman 2] Thief!
- Thief! Somebody help!
- Quick! Catch him!
- What? Ow! What is it?
- [women chattering]
I'm not a thief. I'm a lawyer.
[overlapping chatter]
- Ma'am, please!
- I'm not a thief!
- Calm down. What's going on?
- Please, listen to me. I'm not a thief.
It's him! He was stealing
from Por's house.
- [woman 2] That's right. I saw him.
- [woman 1] Yeah!
I wasn't stealing.
I am an eyewitness.
- [Mek] No, I'm a lawyer!
- You little--
Ma'am, please calm down.
Ma'am, do you remember me?
I'm Dr. Atchara's daughter.
Oh, right. This morning,
she was handing out supplies.
- [Ang] That's right.
- Oh, yeah.
This man is a friend of mine.
He's a lawyer, not a thief.
- What?
- Well…
- [chickens clucking]
- See? I told you.
A handsome man like him?
Are you hurt, dear? Wait, your tumbler.
Oh, here it is. Are you hurt?
- Here, let me help.
- I'm okay, thanks.
If you're a lawyer, why were you
rummaging through Por's house?
Yeah, good point.
Does he have to go to court again?
Something like that.
I knew it. I knew he'd get into trouble
one of these days.
So who filed the complaint?
Was it Kuang or Juk?
He was having trouble with those two?
Yes. And plenty of others, too.
He owes money to everyone around here.
It's no surprise he got arrested.
[woman 1] How much does he owe you?
Over 2,000?
[woman 2 chuckles] He owes me 3,600.
What did he need all that money for?
[woman 2] He spent it all
on his granddaughter.
His son racked up huge baccarat debts…
- Yes.
- …and just ran off.
[woman 2] The debt, the granddaughter…
He was left to handle everything.
But he really does love
his granddaughter.
It's a good thing the fire happened
on his day off.
The guards were changing shifts.
So he got the day off
and took Kratai out.
- Was he a security guard?
- [intriguing music playing]
Where did he work as a guard?
Oh, at the waste processing plant
that burned down.
Wait. If Por gets sued and goes to jail,
how will Kratai survive?
- [woman 1] How should I know?
- Excuse me, ma'am.
Could you tell me the story
about Kratai's father again?
[music fades]
[Ang] So he claimed
to be the factory owner?
[Mek] He said he's a managing director
and a shareholder. Can you believe that?
[Ang] The waste at that factory
is all electronic.
[Mek] Hmm.
It must have been illegally imported.
[Mek] Hmm…
And to open it in a residential area,
the real owner must be well-connected.
Getting your human rights lawyer
blood pumping again, huh?
- [chuckles softly]
- Do you miss it?
I still secretly help the labor union
with their cases.
But my party work is so demanding.
It's a strange sight.
I never thought I'd see it.
[chuckles] Aren't you hot?
I've never heard you use
your mom's name before.
I don't like to.
But mentioning her name
makes it easier to connect with people.
[Mek] Hmm…
So, are you getting used to it?
What about you?
Has taking on public defender cases
made life any better?
It's okay.
It's only been three months.
How okay did you expect me to be?
[soft somber music playing]
What did I do wrong?
Can you tell me now?
I have to get back to work.
Sorry.
- [Mek] Ang.
- [Ang] Mek, just go home.
[Mek] Go home? We need to talk first.
Ang, don't walk away.
3 MONTHS AGO
You don't even answer my calls.
- I'm busy, Mek.
- Busy with what?
You're not doing anything.
Working on what?
Why are you going back on your word?
Aren't you ashamed? Seriously.
Working for a corrupt party like this?
This is my mother's party.
This work is important.
What about your work at the law center?
The people there weren't important?
So many people
entrusted their lives to you.
Like Tle's case. Who's handling it now?
The speech case?
Are you just going to let them all
go to jail?
[soft tense music playing]
You left the law center
because of me, didn't you?
What did I do wrong?
Tell me just one thing.
Ever since you came back
from the party on the boat,
you haven't been the same.
What exactly happened on that boat?
I wanted to break up.
You didn't do anything wrong.
[music concludes]
I just wanted to break up.
- [footsteps departing]
- [soft pensive music playing]
[soft pensive music continues]
[chains jangling]
Sir, I know you didn't do it.
But I don't know what they offered you.
But please, think carefully.
You won't be there for Kratai.
[music concludes]
You're paying off
your son's baccarat debt, right?
So you had to take the fall
for the factory owners.
Please, think this through.
If you go to prison now,
the only one left to look after Kratai
will be your son.
Right? That lump sum you got,
how many years of tuition will it cover?
But if you retract your confession today…
Sir.
I promise I'll do everything
to get you the lightest sentence possible.
[Aon] What are you doing?
Please trust me.
I'm speaking with my client.
What's with you?
- He's my father.
- Calm down, son.
- What did you say to him?
- [Mek] Officer.
- None of your damn business!
- How did you let a drunk man in?
Dad, don't listen to him. I told you.
Officer, please remove him.
- [officer] Sir, please leave.
- Are you messing with me?
[officer] Please step outside.
I need to talk to my father.
I have the right!
Dad!
- Don't talk to him anymore!
- Sir, trust me.
The only person you need to think about
is Kratai.
- [Aon shouting indistinctly]
- Okay?
Please trust me.
The court will explain
the defendant's rights
before proceeding with the trial.
Do you plead guilty to all charges?
Well, defendant?
[Mek softly] Sir.
[judge] Defendant.
The defendant pleads not guilty
to all charges.
Let me explain.
From the beginning, the defendant
has not had a chance to consult a lawyer.
And I believe that is his basic right.
If he is truly not guilty, he should have
the right to fight, correct?
Today, I've prepared documents that I…
I am addressing the defendant.
Let him answer.
So, how do you plead, defendant?
[clock ticking faintly]
Sir.
[Por] I…
I… I'm not guilty.
[soft pensive music playing]
I'll fight the charges.
[breathes deeply]
[grunts softly]
Sir, I'll start the bail process
right away.
Then we can fight this from the outside.
Thank you so much.
[chains jangling]
[Techin] Hey.
Just so you know,
this case is bigger than you think.
Bigger how?
I'm just doing my job.
- [music fades]
- What is wrong with you?
I already told you, didn't I?
That I won't let him go to prison.
[scoffs]
But are you going to tell me
who the factory owner is?
Some guy with dirty money?
Or is it your dad?
I gave you a friendly warning.
But you just wouldn't listen.
[foreboding music playing]
[foreboding music continues]
[seat belt clicks]
[Techin] Dad.
About the waste plant fire case,
it might drag on a little longer
than we thought.
My senior, Mek, has taken the case.
He's…
But don't worry, Dad.
I can definitely handle him.
That 3-iron I gave you.
Have you been practicing?
[unsettling music playing]
[bucket clangs]
[Anan] Focus.
You see…
not everyone gets equal opportunities.
[tense music playing]
Every time someone gives you
a chance to do something,
you must remember that…
it's because they trust you.
If you give someone your word,
you have to keep it.
Because if you can't…
you won't be the one
who ends up the most disappointed.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
[music builds]
[golf club thwacks]
[music fades]
[foreboding music playing]
- [pen clicking]
- [indistinct chatter]
[cell phone ringing]
TAE - CLASS OF '49
- [cell phone clicks]
- [ringing stops]
[cell phone buzzes, chimes]
DEPOSIT: 300,000 BAHT
OCT 14, 2025
[dial tone ringing]
[sighs]
[dial tone continues ringing]
Is this the only way you know
how to play?
[Techin] Play what?
I'm not playing. I'm dead serious.
[snickers]
What I sent you was just a deposit.
The moment you drop the case,
I'll transfer the rest.
Listen, if you don't quit this shit,
I'll report you to the Lawyers Council.
[Techin] I knew it.
Money alone could never sway
a good man like you.
I've prepared a little surprise for you.
Do you want to know
why Ang broke up with you?
What does Ang have to do with this?
[Techin] Remember three months ago?
After that party on the boat,
Ang started acting weird, right?
And then she left you.
Why was that? [chuckles]
[tense music playing]
Ang would never dare tell you.
But I will.
Come and see me.
I'm at my house in Saraburi.
You remember it, right?
But you only have until tonight.
If you don't show up,
you'll just have to guess
what I'll do with what I know.
[cell phone chimes]
[music rises]
[Mek] What is it?
What happened?
[Ang] Nothing happened.
[Mek] Were you lying to me?
[music fades]
[Mek] It was on the boat, wasn't it?
What happened at the party?
Did somebody do something to you?
You have to tell me.
I can help you fix this.
[Ang] You can't, Mek.
Even if I told you, you couldn't help.
[foreboding music playing]
[engine revving]
[foreboding music continues]
[brakes screeching]
[gearshift clunks]
[handbrake creaks]
[insects trilling]
[Techin] That was fast.
You must've floored it.
- [music concludes]
- Wow. Less than two hours.
That's the new record.
Here's your money.
Now, what do you have to say?
Since you drove all the way here,
how about we play a hole?
I just got a new caddie, too.
Hey!
If you have nothing to say, I'm leaving.
Alright, calm down, Mek.
We can talk while we play.
It's not that hard.
This is Nay Oo.
- You bitch!
- [tense music playing]
[Techin] I told you not to drag it!
Don't you understand what I said?
- What is wrong with you?
- Hey!
The bag's heavy as hell.
Why don't you carry it?
Fine. You want to play so bad? One hole.
That's it. [chuckles]
After you.
Go.
[Mek] Here, let me get that.
I'm fine, sir.
[bag rustling]
[music concludes]
- [indistinct clamor over radio]
- [radio host speaking indistinctly]
- [indistinct clamor continues]
- [radio host continues speaking]
[chuckles]
Nailed it.
Show me what you've got.
[golf club thwacks]
Damn. You really crushed that.
You picturing my head
when you swing? [laughs]
Still, your form's not bad. Passable.
So, how many years has it been, Mek?
I never see you at the reunions.
You still play much?
So, what is it?
Are you going to tell me or not?
What's the rush?
[scoffs]
Alright.
[zipper opens]
[zipper closes]
[unsettling music playing]
You want it or not?
[scoffs] What the hell
are you so paranoid about?
Huh? You know I'm not usually this nice.
Don't you want to know…
why Ang broke up with you?
The answer's in here.
[folder thuds]
MYSTERIOUS BODY
FOUND IN CHAO PHRAYA RIVER
Hey, what the hell is this?
Do you remember the date
of that party on the boat?
I'll answer for you.
July 1st.
Check the date in the article.
July 10th.
"The body of a foreign woman discovered…
floating in the Chao Phraya River."
And I've got something else.
An exclusive, just for you.
What are you trying to say?
And what does Ang have to do with this?
[Techin] At the party,
a waitress on that boat died.
And on a boat that small…
You think Ang didn't know?
Of course, she knew…
but why did she cover it up?
[chuckles]
She'd just gotten into politics.
If word got out that she helped
dispose of a body… [clicks tongue]
Game over.
You're using this to get me
to drop the factory case, aren't you?
[scoffs] I didn't say that.
But maybe.
You don't have the guts, Techin.
If you leak this, you go down.
So do your dad and everyone on that boat.
Oh! Damn it.
Enough talk. Go get the ball.
You're right.
I have no intention of leaking anything.
Neither does anyone else on the boat.
Why would they risk
getting themselves into trouble?
[scoffs]
Everyone on that boat was a VVIP.
No one's stupid enough to risk it all
for one Burmese girl.
But someone with nothing to lose?
Someone with absolutely nothing to lose.
You never know
when they might turn on you.
- What are you talking about?
- [Techin] Hey, wait.
Remember this woman?
Was she on the boat with you
the night your sister died?
[tense dramatic music playing]
- [Nay Oo yelps]
- [Mek] Hey! What are you doing?
Are you okay?
- [Nay Oo whimpers]
- [Mek] What the hell is wrong with you?!
Now do you get it?
The waitress who died was her sister.
And she was on the boat that night.
If she decides to talk,
everyone from that boat goes down.
But if she disappears, it's all over.
What the hell are you saying?
Who's going to disappear?
[music intensifies]
[Mek] What the hell are you doing?!
[groans]
[discordant tense music playing]
- [gunshots]
- [glass shatters]
- [breathes shakily]
- [high-pitched ringing]
[woman echoing] Help!
[breathes shakily]
What the hell is wrong with you?
- Are you hurt?
- [Techin laughs]
[Nay Oo sobs]
That was just practice.
This time, it's for real.
- Why are you doing this?
- I'm helping Ang eliminate the evidence.
Her sister is dead.
How long do you think she'll stay quiet?
Are you kidding me? Look at her.
She's scared to death.
You won't say anything, right?
[sobbing] I swear. I won't say anything.
I'll go back home to Myanmar.
- I swear, sir.
- [chuckles]
[Mek] You know the court
won't give her word any weight.
It's just the word of one witness, right?
And she's the victim's relative.
You know that.
I don't think that's good enough.
Don't!
You want me to drop the case?
Fine. I'll go sign the papers right now.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
You drop the case,
then you just have your client--
- [thud]
- [grunts, coughs]
- [Nay Oo sobbing]
- [music builds]
[Nay Oo sobs]
[music crescendos]
- [gunshot echoes]
- [music concludes]
[Techin laughs]
[in English] Nice shot, bro.
[somber music playing]
[Techin in Thai]
We're in the same boat now.
If the cops test this gun,
they'll find both of our fingerprints.
That means there are two suspects.
You'll be going to prison
right alongside me.
[snickers]
Stay away from the waste plant case.
What are you so shocked about, huh?
You're acting like you've never seen
someone get shot before.
[echoing gunshots]
- [Techin] Oh…
- [breathes shakily]
[Techin] Does little Mek miss his mommy?
[laughs]
I feel you, bro.
But your family's story is something else.
Your dad's a legendary judge,
isn't he? [laughs]
Sacrificed his wife for his principles.
[Nay Oo yells]
[groans]
[shrieks]
- [breathes shakily]
- [music concludes]
[Nay Oo grunts]
- [sobbing]
- [heavy thuds]
- [wailing]
- [squelching]
[dark tense music playing]
- That's enough.
- [music fades]
- [sobs]
[foreboding music playing]
[sobbing]
[whimpering]
[breathes shakily]
[Nay Oo sobbing]
[Mek breathing shakily]
[man echoing] Sir! Help me!
[reporter 1] Our reporter
on the scene confirms
the suspect has been apprehended.
He was arrested at the scene.
The suspect has been identified
as Mek Piriyawich.
[reporter 2] We have a report
coming from our sources.
The victim was Techin Methaneepaisal.
The victim was the son of Pol. Gen. Anan.
That's Police General Anan Methaneepaisal.
[reporter 1] The police currently have
the suspect in custody for questioning.
A decision regarding bail
is currently pending.
[sound becomes muffled]
[foreboding music continues]
[dramatic musical sting plays]
[Nay Oo sobbing, echoing]
[echoing heavy thuds]
[Nay Oo shrieks]
[music turns intriguing]
We don't have much time.
If you want to survive, listen carefully.
Because I'm your only way out.
[dramatic music overlapping]
[music intensifies]
[dark tense music playing]
[music concludes]